## Mohammed Parvez

Hyderabad, Telangana mohammedshoyebparvez8\_ng8@indeedemail.com +91 7416139121

Web developer with 5 years of experience in Developing dynamic and interactive websites and portals, experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects, maintained interactive and user friendly features that improve user interaction and workflow efficiency.

### Work Experience

#### wed developer

iPrism Technologies Pvt Ltd October 2019 to October 2019

- Rest API development for Android and iOS using php
- Develope user module and admin module
- Add enhancement features in previous project

#### web developer

thinkFair Web Technologies September 2018 to February 2019

#### web developer

OmkielT Solutions Pvt Ltd June 2015 to August 2018

- Experience of Interacting with the client & understanding requirements.
- Developement of website admin panel and user module

#### Education

# **B.Tech in Electronics & Telecommunication in Electronics & Telecommunication**

SRTM University 2014

S. S. C

Sana School

2007

#### Skills / IT Skills

· Language: PHP

• Framework: Codelgniter

• Databases: MySQL.

- Front-End Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Rest API.
- Tools: Netbeans, SQLyog.